oh i don't think that julian assange
revealed any sources and methods i think
that julian's crime was embarrassing uh
the powers that be in washington you
know one of the red herrings that the
federal government uses in every one of
these cases is they say that sources and
methods were revealed and that the lives
of either american diplomats or our war
fighters serving overseas were placed in
danger they did say that with julian but
could never offer any proof just like
they couldn't offer proof with ed
snowden or with chelsea manning so i
don't believe that there was any
damage to the national security uh i
don't think that we should take
seriously american accusations that
there was damage to the national
security julian assange has shown that
a
german citizen
was
kidnapped by cia
a cia snatch team and tortured and
sodomized in a cia black site in a case
of mistaken identity and then was just
let go
if it weren't for julian assange and
wikileaks we wouldn't even know about
this case
this is
the there are so many cases like it you
also have cablegate where we saw
the state department engaging in illegal
activity in sovereign countries to
topple their government training
opposition figures uh that we saw
through the stratfor cables exposed on
wikileaks training opposition figures
like juan guido and his mentor leopoldo
lopez to overthrow the venezuelan
government plotting to uh sabotage dams
inside venezuela to help overthrow hugo
chavez the list goes on and on and on
these are details few journalists even
know and that's why i think
they're after assange and are seeking to
kill him in slow motion by prolonging
his imprisonment for as long as possible